onlive.co.uk 2015-04-28

# Privacy Policy | OnLive Games

#### Legal

OnLive Privacy Policy Effective Date: March 5, 2014 OL2, Inc. and its group of companies (collectively, "OnLive" or "we" or "us") respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect on the following, which we will refer to as the "OnLive Services" or the "Services": * onlive.com and any other OnLive-owned websites that link to this Privacy Policy (the "OnLive Websites" or "Websites") * OnLive Game Service; * OnLive Desktop; * Other OnLive-owned apps and software that link to this Privacy Policy; and * OnLive Customer Service ("OnLive CS"). Our Services offer connectivity with a growing number of services provided by third parties, such as social networks, content providers, platforms, communications tools, plugins and widgets of many varieties (collectively, "Third Party Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services. Third Party Services' privacy practices are subject to their own policies. By using the Services, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 1\. Information We Obtain Information You Submit You may choose to provide us with information through the Services, such as: * Contact information, such as your name, email address, telephone number and mailing address. * Date of birth. * Information obtained from the Facebook account you associate with the Services and all information available to us through the Facebook Application Programming Interface. * Login credentials for Third Party Services that you would like to use through the Services. * Payment card information and related billing details. * Communications within our Services (such as email, instant messaging sessions, video, text chats, voice communications, friend requests, and online group activity) and related information. We may monitor all communications taking place through our Services. For example, if a user of the OnLive Game Service uses voice chat to talk to another user, their conversation may be recorded as part of a Brag Clip® video. * Other content you submit or create on the Services. * Information relevant to candidacy for employment with us, such as your resume, if you apply for a job with us. Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software In general, when you use the apps and other software that are part of the OnLive Service, we may collect the following information by automated means: * Information about your computer or other device and related hardware, including identification details (e.g., MAC address). * Information about your operating system, platform and other software you use in connection with the Services. * IP address of your device. * Information about your network connection and your ISP. * The times of your connection to our Services. * Information about your use of the software. * Your interactions with or communications through certain Third Party Services or other information about your use of certain Third Party Services, in connection with the Service, (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). Please see the following sections for more details regarding automated collection by the OnLive Game Service and OnLive Desktop. OnLive Game Service In addition to the information discussed in the introduction to the "Information We Collect by Automated Means with Apps and Other Software" section, the OnLive Game Service also uses automated means to collect and create information such as the following: * All of your gameplay, including everything you hear, see, say or do while playing or otherwise interacting with a game or its settings. This includes, for example, all voice chat, notifications, friend requests and responses, and all other communications with the Services and with other people that take place within the game, as well as your Player Tag or Screen Name. * Player Profiles, which are a combination of information you submit and information we collect by automated means. These personal summaries may include the user's Player Tag, presence on the Services, last log-on, use of content, gameplay statistics, and stated city, region or country location that can be seen on the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service. * All other aspects of your interaction with the OnLive Game Service, such as your interaction with its main settings. OnLive Desktop In addition to the discussion in the introduction to the "Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software" section, please note the following regarding OnLive Desktop's automated collection of information: * The applications available in the OnLive Desktop service function much like they do when you use them locally on a computer. Thus if you choose to store passwords, bookmarks, or browsing history or to allow cookies to be stored in Internet Explorer in the OnLive Desktop Service, that information will be stored by the program itself at your direction. Pursuant to Internet Explorer's own security measures, passwords and login information are encrypted just as they would be on your own computer. You thus can exercise certain choices regarding the information Internet Explorer and other programs available in the OnLive Desktop Service store and collect using the privacy controls and preference functions in those programs. * While accessing or using OnLive Desktop, you may create or download information, such as data files, written text, computer software, music, audio files or other sounds, photographs, videos or other images, and communications of every variety ("Your Desktop Content"). * The information described in this OnLive Desktop subsection is for your individual use, and we do not otherwise use or disclose the information in connection with providing and supporting the relevant Services and as described in the "Other Sharing" section below. Information We Collect by Automated Means on Our Websites * When you use our Websites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, Clear GIFs, and website and service logs (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). * Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your computer or other Internet access device. Cookies may enable us to personalize your experience on the Websites, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information about your computer and monitor advertisements and other activities. For example, cookies can advise us whether you have visited one of the OnLive Websites previously, and/or may contain other information that will facilitate your next visit to one of the OnLive Websites. Cookies do not include or collect personal information but rather, they may identify your computer. Our Websites may use HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html] and Global Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html]. The decision to disable cookies, however, may prevent you from being able to use certain portions of the OnLive Websites. * Clear GIFs: Clear GIFs are small graphic images (in GIF or other image format) placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-1 pixel) and either transparent or the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. We may, however, use clear GIFs on our Websites to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages. We do not use clear GIFs in the OnLive Game Service or OnLive Desktop Service. * Website & Service Logs: OnLive may collect information in the form of website and/or service logs (collectively "Logs"). These Logs are files that record activity on the Websites and related Services and gather statistics about users' activities, such as how many users have visited the Websites, how often, how many "hits" a particular webpage has received, sign-in and sign-off times for the Services, type and quality of the user's Internet connection to the Services, identification of the user's hardware and software running the Services, which features on the Services you used, and the frequency of use. The entries comprising the Logs may contain IP addresses, user IDs, email addresses, and identification of the Internet service provider that provides your connection to the Internet. Generally, we may use the Logs to (i) operate and improve the Websites and Services; (ii) identify the popularity of certain features; (iii) assist with marketing and demographic studies; (iv) enable us to assess overall efficiency and activity on the Websites and Services; and (v) assess users' web-browsing, usage, preferences, and habits on the Websites and in the OnLive Game Service. We also use the Logs to monitor traffic on the Websites and Services, to troubleshoot technical problems, to support OnLive CS operations, for security reasons, and to foster the safety of the Websites and Services. Please note that Third Party Services may collect personally identifiable information about an individual's online activities over time and across different Web sites when the individual uses our Website and other Services. The Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. If OnLive becomes aware that any person submitting information to the Services is under the age of 13, we will promptly take steps to delete or anonymize the information and may close the Account pursuant to the OnLive Terms of Service. 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect In General We may use the information we collect through the Services to provide the Services and fulfill the immediate purpose for which it was requested, as well as for other purposes. Uses may include: * Providing, administering and communicating with you about products, services, events and promotions for us and our business partners (including by contacting you with newsletters and other marketing communications). * Processing, evaluating and responding to your requests, inquiries and applications. * Managing our customer information databases. * Administering contests, sweepstakes and surveys and other communications. * Customizing your experience with our Services. * Evaluating your application for employment with us. * Creating marketing content. * Operating, evaluating and improving our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research, data analytics and data appends; determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; analyzing our products and services; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities). * Protecting against and preventing fraud, unauthorized transactions, security issues, claims and other liabilities, and managing risk exposure and quality for our Services and Third Party Services. * Complying with and enforcing applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms, such as our Terms of Service for our Services and terms imposed by Third Party Services. Analytics We may use third-party Web analytics services on our Websites, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use the sort of technology described in the Information We Collect by Automated Means on Our Websites section to help us analyze how users use the Websites, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive. The information collected by the technology (including your IP address) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Websites. We also may use data from Google's interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as interests) with Google Analytics to understand our audiences. To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please click here [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout]. 3\. Sharing of Information We may share your information in a variety of ways as we provide the Services and our business evolves. * When someone becomes your friend, that person (as well as that person's friends and those friends' friends) will have access to information about what games you are playing and have played as well as your communications within the Services, a list of your friends, your Player Profile, your Brag Clip™ videos, your last visit to the OnLive Game Service, date joined, total play time, play style, and motto. * By default, the Spectating feature on the OnLive Game Service makes available to all users of the OnLive Game Service continuous live viewing of your gameplay. The Brag Clip™ videos feature allows you to record short clips of your gameplay that may be viewed by others. Any notifications a user receives during game play (including notifications about the person playing the game or about other users in the Service), as well as the Player Tag of the person playing the game or of other users about whom the notification has been sent, may be visible during Spectating and in Brag Clip videos. Because live gameplay or other activity in the OnLive Game Service may be widely viewed through the Spectating feature, and may be captured in Brag Clip videos, OnLive cautions users to avoid revealing personally identifiable information during gameplay or other activity on the Services such as when using voice chat or text. If at any time a user does not limit Spectating of their gameplay or the viewing of Brag Clip videos, OnLive may from that point forward use such videos or live gameplay both on the Services and externally for other purposes, including demonstrations, tournaments, marketing, promotional efforts, game refinement, engineering analysis or any other purpose. * We may share information with the Third Party Services with which you choose to interact, such as by posting to your social media account. For further detail about Facebook-related sharing, visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22280346-facebook-sharing]. * We may share your information among our affiliates and joint marketing partners. * We may provide a report to our business partners that tells them who responded to a particular offer or to facilitate the fulfillment of an order that you have made with a business partner. * To help your friends find you, OnLive may allow registered users who enter your email address to find you and send you friend requests through the OnLive Game Service. For more information and instructions on how to opt out of others finding you via your email address please visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22278213-Privacy-Settings]. Other Sharing * We share your information to facilitate your requests or in connection with such requests, such as when you use features specifically designed for sharing. For example, if you provide us with login credentials for a Third Party Service so that we may log you into that service, we will provide the Third Party Service with those credentials to carry out your request. * We may share information we collect on the Services with certain service providers that support our Services or perform work on our behalf. * We may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury or loss; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. * We reserve the right to transfer information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation). * We also may disclose aggregated information to third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users. Please note: * We do not consider Player Tags, Screen Names or Player Profiles to be personal information. We may use and disclose them without restriction. For example, Player Tags and Player Profiles from the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service (as well as the username for the Third Party Service that you use in connection with the Service) may be made public for the purposes of leaderboards, enhancing multiplayer gameplay, tournaments, marketing and promotion efforts and other business activities. The same is true of demographic information we collect through surveys (such as personal tastes and purchasing habits), unless we indicate otherwise in connection with a particular survey. * The sharing preferences within our Services generally do not affect the sharing of any information by or within Third Party Services. For more information, please see the "Your Rights and Choices" section below. 4\. Data Transfers and Safe Harbor We may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable law. As described in our Safe Harbor certification [http://safeharbor.export.gov/companyinfo.aspx?id=19081], we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information received in the U.S. from European Union member countries and Switzerland. OL2, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view OL2, Inc.'s certification, please visit the Safe Harbor website [http://export.gov/safeharbor/]. If you have any questions or complaints about our handling of your personal information that we receive in connection with Safe Harbor, please contact us as described in the "How to Contact Us" section below. If we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may contact the ESRB, and we agree to resolve the matter through their processes. 5\. Your Rights and Choices Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. Where applicable, you may amend your preferences regarding how we communicate with you and make certain other privacy-related choices by updating your profile, account and settings in your OnLive authenticated account or by contacting us as described in the How to Contact Us section below. You may unsubscribe from OnLive marketing-oriented emails by following the instructions in those emails. As this Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services, and because we do not control Third Party Services, exercising your rights and choices under this section of the Privacy Policy will not affect the Third Party Services' handling of your information. For example, the Privacy preferences screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service allows you to limit how the extent to which the OnLive Game Service itself shares your Brag Clip® videos within the OnLive Game Service. That setting applies only within the OnLive Game Service. If you access games through a Third Party Service, the Third Party Service's sharing settings — and not the sharing settings of the OnLive Game Service itself — will apply to how the Third Party Service shares information. Be sure to familiarize yourself with the privacy settings — and their defaults — of each Third Party Service with which you interact, as they generally operate independently from those of the OnLive Services. In some cases, we may build features into our Services that are specially designed to allow you to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. These features will be clearly labeled to highlight this functionality. For example, you can use the Facebook Sharing screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service to make certain adjustments to what the OnLive Game Service will ask Facebook to post to your wall. In some cases, settings within the Third Party Services may be used to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. For example, a Third Party Services may allow you to enter an authentication key or other credential through our OnLive Game Service that may allow you to remain logged in to the Third Party Service through our OnLive Game Service, even when you are not using the OnLive Game Service; you may be able to contact the Third Party Service to revoke that credential or adjust how it works. 6\. Notice to California Customers Unless they opt in, we do not share the "personal information" of California customers with third parties for those third parties' "direct marketing purposes" as those terms are used in California Civil Code § 1798.83. To opt in, California residents may contact us as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section below. 7\. Security Although we may take certain precautions that we believe may help protect against unauthorized access to our Services, no security is perfect. We make no promises regarding the security, integrity, availability or retention of the information collected or handled by our Services or related systems. For more details, please review the "Disclaimers" and "Limitation of Liability" sections of our Terms of Service. 8\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. To inform you of any change, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on onlive.com and indicate at the top of the Privacy Policy when it was updated. We may also choose to notify you by email. 9\. ESRB Certification This Privacy Policy and the certification seal confirm that OnLive is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board ("ESRB") Privacy Certified Program. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. The ESRB has reviewed and certified that the OnLive Services meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of the ESRB certification program, we are subject to frequent audits of our Websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. 10\. How to Contact Us If you have any comments, questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please send us a detailed message via email at privacy@onlive.com or via regular mail to OnLive, 1091 N. Shoreline Boulevard, Suite 100, Mountain View, California 94043, Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator and Legal Department. Thank you. 

OnLive Privacy Policy Effective Date: March 5, 2014 OL2, Inc. and its group of companies (collectively, "OnLive" or "we" or "us") respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect on the following, which we will refer to as the "OnLive Services" or the "Services": * onlive.com and any other OnLive-owned websites that link to this Privacy Policy (the "OnLive Websites" or "Websites") * OnLive Game Service; * OnLive Desktop; * Other OnLive-owned apps and software that link to this Privacy Policy; and * OnLive Customer Service ("OnLive CS"). Our Services offer connectivity with a growing number of services provided by third parties, such as social networks, content providers, platforms, communications tools, plugins and widgets of many varieties (collectively, "Third Party Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services. Third Party Services' privacy practices are subject to their own policies. By using the Services, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 1\. Information We Obtain Information You Submit You may choose to provide us with information through the Services, such as: * Contact information, such as your name, email address, telephone number and mailing address. * Date of birth. * Information obtained from the Facebook account you associate with the Services and all information available to us through the Facebook Application Programming Interface. * Login credentials for Third Party Services that you would like to use through the Services. * Payment card information and related billing details. * Communications within our Services (such as email, instant messaging sessions, video, text chats, voice communications, friend requests, and online group activity) and related information. We may monitor all communications taking place through our Services. For example, if a user of the OnLive Game Service uses voice chat to talk to another user, their conversation may be recorded as part of a Brag Clip® video. * Other content you submit or create on the Services. * Information relevant to candidacy for employment with us, such as your resume, if you apply for a job with us. Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software In general, when you use the apps and other software that are part of the OnLive Service, we may collect the following information by automated means: * Information about your computer or other device and related hardware, including identification details (e.g., MAC address). * Information about your operating system, platform and other software you use in connection with the Services. * IP address of your device. * Information about your network connection and your ISP. * The times of your connection to our Services. * Information about your use of the software. * Your interactions with or communications through certain Third Party Services or other information about your use of certain Third Party Services, in connection with the Service, (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). Please see the following sections for more details regarding automated collection by the OnLive Game Service and OnLive Desktop. OnLive Game Service In addition to the information discussed in the introduction to the "Information We Collect by Automated Means with Apps and Other Software" section, the OnLive Game Service also uses automated means to collect and create information such as the following: * All of your gameplay, including everything you hear, see, say or do while playing or otherwise interacting with a game or its settings. This includes, for example, all voice chat, notifications, friend requests and responses, and all other communications with the Services and with other people that take place within the game, as well as your Player Tag or Screen Name. * Player Profiles, which are a combination of information you submit and information we collect by automated means. These personal summaries may include the user's Player Tag, presence on the Services, last log-on, use of content, gameplay statistics, and stated city, region or country location that can be seen on the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service. * All other aspects of your interaction with the OnLive Game Service, such as your interaction with its main settings. OnLive Desktop In addition to the discussion in the introduction to the "Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software" section, please note the following regarding OnLive Desktop's automated collection of information: * The applications available in the OnLive Desktop service function much like they do when you use them locally on a computer. Thus if you choose to store passwords, bookmarks, or browsing history or to allow cookies to be stored in Internet Explorer in the OnLive Desktop Service, that information will be stored by the program itself at your direction. Pursuant to Internet Explorer's own security measures, passwords and login information are encrypted just as they would be on your own computer. You thus can exercise certain choices regarding the information Internet Explorer and other programs available in the OnLive Desktop Service store and collect using the privacy controls and preference functions in those programs. * While accessing or using OnLive Desktop, you may create or download information, such as data files, written text, computer software, music, audio files or other sounds, photographs, videos or other images, and communications of every variety ("Your Desktop Content"). * The information described in this OnLive Desktop subsection is for your individual use, and we do not otherwise use or disclose the information in connection with providing and supporting the relevant Services and as described in the "Other Sharing" section below. Information We Collect by Automated Means on Our Websites * When you use our Websites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, Clear GIFs, and website and service logs (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). * Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your computer or other Internet access device. Cookies may enable us to personalize your experience on the Websites, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information about your computer and monitor advertisements and other activities. For example, cookies can advise us whether you have visited one of the OnLive Websites previously, and/or may contain other information that will facilitate your next visit to one of the OnLive Websites. Cookies do not include or collect personal information but rather, they may identify your computer. Our Websites may use HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html] and Global Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html]. The decision to disable cookies, however, may prevent you from being able to use certain portions of the OnLive Websites. * Clear GIFs: Clear GIFs are small graphic images (in GIF or other image format) placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-1 pixel) and either transparent or the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. We may, however, use clear GIFs on our Websites to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages. We do not use clear GIFs in the OnLive Game Service or OnLive Desktop Service. * Website & Service Logs: OnLive may collect information in the form of website and/or service logs (collectively "Logs"). These Logs are files that record activity on the Websites and related Services and gather statistics about users' activities, such as how many users have visited the Websites, how often, how many "hits" a particular webpage has received, sign-in and sign-off times for the Services, type and quality of the user's Internet connection to the Services, identification of the user's hardware and software running the Services, which features on the Services you used, and the frequency of use. The entries comprising the Logs may contain IP addresses, user IDs, email addresses, and identification of the Internet service provider that provides your connection to the Internet. Generally, we may use the Logs to (i) operate and improve the Websites and Services; (ii) identify the popularity of certain features; (iii) assist with marketing and demographic studies; (iv) enable us to assess overall efficiency and activity on the Websites and Services; and (v) assess users' web-browsing, usage, preferences, and habits on the Websites and in the OnLive Game Service. We also use the Logs to monitor traffic on the Websites and Services, to troubleshoot technical problems, to support OnLive CS operations, for security reasons, and to foster the safety of the Websites and Services. Please note that Third Party Services may collect personally identifiable information about an individual's online activities over time and across different Web sites when the individual uses our Website and other Services. The Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. If OnLive becomes aware that any person submitting information to the Services is under the age of 13, we will promptly take steps to delete or anonymize the information and may close the Account pursuant to the OnLive Terms of Service. 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect In General We may use the information we collect through the Services to provide the Services and fulfill the immediate purpose for which it was requested, as well as for other purposes. Uses may include: * Providing, administering and communicating with you about products, services, events and promotions for us and our business partners (including by contacting you with newsletters and other marketing communications). * Processing, evaluating and responding to your requests, inquiries and applications. * Managing our customer information databases. * Administering contests, sweepstakes and surveys and other communications. * Customizing your experience with our Services. * Evaluating your application for employment with us. * Creating marketing content. * Operating, evaluating and improving our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research, data analytics and data appends; determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; analyzing our products and services; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities). * Protecting against and preventing fraud, unauthorized transactions, security issues, claims and other liabilities, and managing risk exposure and quality for our Services and Third Party Services. * Complying with and enforcing applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms, such as our Terms of Service for our Services and terms imposed by Third Party Services. Analytics We may use third-party Web analytics services on our Websites, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use the sort of technology described in the Information We Collect by Automated Means on Our Websites section to help us analyze how users use the Websites, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive. The information collected by the technology (including your IP address) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Websites. We also may use data from Google's interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as interests) with Google Analytics to understand our audiences. To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please click here [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout]. 3\. Sharing of Information We may share your information in a variety of ways as we provide the Services and our business evolves. * When someone becomes your friend, that person (as well as that person's friends and those friends' friends) will have access to information about what games you are playing and have played as well as your communications within the Services, a list of your friends, your Player Profile, your Brag Clip™ videos, your last visit to the OnLive Game Service, date joined, total play time, play style, and motto. * By default, the Spectating feature on the OnLive Game Service makes available to all users of the OnLive Game Service continuous live viewing of your gameplay. The Brag Clip™ videos feature allows you to record short clips of your gameplay that may be viewed by others. Any notifications a user receives during game play (including notifications about the person playing the game or about other users in the Service), as well as the Player Tag of the person playing the game or of other users about whom the notification has been sent, may be visible during Spectating and in Brag Clip videos. Because live gameplay or other activity in the OnLive Game Service may be widely viewed through the Spectating feature, and may be captured in Brag Clip videos, OnLive cautions users to avoid revealing personally identifiable information during gameplay or other activity on the Services such as when using voice chat or text. If at any time a user does not limit Spectating of their gameplay or the viewing of Brag Clip videos, OnLive may from that point forward use such videos or live gameplay both on the Services and externally for other purposes, including demonstrations, tournaments, marketing, promotional efforts, game refinement, engineering analysis or any other purpose. * We may share information with the Third Party Services with which you choose to interact, such as by posting to your social media account. For further detail about Facebook-related sharing, visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22280346-facebook-sharing]. * We may share your information among our affiliates and joint marketing partners. * We may provide a report to our business partners that tells them who responded to a particular offer or to facilitate the fulfillment of an order that you have made with a business partner. * To help your friends find you, OnLive may allow registered users who enter your email address to find you and send you friend requests through the OnLive Game Service. For more information and instructions on how to opt out of others finding you via your email address please visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22278213-Privacy-Settings]. Other Sharing * We share your information to facilitate your requests or in connection with such requests, such as when you use features specifically designed for sharing. For example, if you provide us with login credentials for a Third Party Service so that we may log you into that service, we will provide the Third Party Service with those credentials to carry out your request. * We may share information we collect on the Services with certain service providers that support our Services or perform work on our behalf. * We may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury or loss; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. * We reserve the right to transfer information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation). * We also may disclose aggregated information to third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users. Please note: * We do not consider Player Tags, Screen Names or Player Profiles to be personal information. We may use and disclose them without restriction. For example, Player Tags and Player Profiles from the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service (as well as the username for the Third Party Service that you use in connection with the Service) may be made public for the purposes of leaderboards, enhancing multiplayer gameplay, tournaments, marketing and promotion efforts and other business activities. The same is true of demographic information we collect through surveys (such as personal tastes and purchasing habits), unless we indicate otherwise in connection with a particular survey. * The sharing preferences within our Services generally do not affect the sharing of any information by or within Third Party Services. For more information, please see the "Your Rights and Choices" section below. 4\. Data Transfers and Safe Harbor We may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable law. As described in our Safe Harbor certification [http://safeharbor.export.gov/companyinfo.aspx?id=19081], we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information received in the U.S. from European Union member countries and Switzerland. OL2, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view OL2, Inc.'s certification, please visit the Safe Harbor website [http://export.gov/safeharbor/]. If you have any questions or complaints about our handling of your personal information that we receive in connection with Safe Harbor, please contact us as described in the "How to Contact Us" section below. If we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may contact the ESRB, and we agree to resolve the matter through their processes. 5\. Your Rights and Choices Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. Where applicable, you may amend your preferences regarding how we communicate with you and make certain other privacy-related choices by updating your profile, account and settings in your OnLive authenticated account or by contacting us as described in the How to Contact Us section below. You may unsubscribe from OnLive marketing-oriented emails by following the instructions in those emails. As this Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services, and because we do not control Third Party Services, exercising your rights and choices under this section of the Privacy Policy will not affect the Third Party Services' handling of your information. For example, the Privacy preferences screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service allows you to limit how the extent to which the OnLive Game Service itself shares your Brag Clip® videos within the OnLive Game Service. That setting applies only within the OnLive Game Service. If you access games through a Third Party Service, the Third Party Service's sharing settings — and not the sharing settings of the OnLive Game Service itself — will apply to how the Third Party Service shares information. Be sure to familiarize yourself with the privacy settings — and their defaults — of each Third Party Service with which you interact, as they generally operate independently from those of the OnLive Services. In some cases, we may build features into our Services that are specially designed to allow you to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. These features will be clearly labeled to highlight this functionality. For example, you can use the Facebook Sharing screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service to make certain adjustments to what the OnLive Game Service will ask Facebook to post to your wall. In some cases, settings within the Third Party Services may be used to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. For example, a Third Party Services may allow you to enter an authentication key or other credential through our OnLive Game Service that may allow you to remain logged in to the Third Party Service through our OnLive Game Service, even when you are not using the OnLive Game Service; you may be able to contact the Third Party Service to revoke that credential or adjust how it works. 6\. Notice to California Customers Unless they opt in, we do not share the "personal information" of California customers with third parties for those third parties' "direct marketing purposes" as those terms are used in California Civil Code § 1798.83. To opt in, California residents may contact us as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section below. 7\. Security Although we may take certain precautions that we believe may help protect against unauthorized access to our Services, no security is perfect. We make no promises regarding the security, integrity, availability or retention of the information collected or handled by our Services or related systems. For more details, please review the "Disclaimers" and "Limitation of Liability" sections of our Terms of Service. 8\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our information practices or relevant laws. To inform you of any change, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on onlive.com and indicate at the top of the Privacy Policy when it was updated. We may also choose to notify you by email. 9\. ESRB Certification This Privacy Policy and the certification seal confirm that OnLive is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board ("ESRB") Privacy Certified Program. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. The ESRB has reviewed and certified that the OnLive Services meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of the ESRB certification program, we are subject to frequent audits of our Websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. 10\. How to Contact Us If you have any comments, questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please send us a detailed message via email at privacy@onlive.com or via regular mail to OnLive, 1091 N. Shoreline Boulevard, Suite 100, Mountain View, California 94043, Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator and Legal Department. Thank you. 

OnLive Privacy Policy Effective Date: March 27, 2014 OnLive EMEA S.à r.l (4, Rue Graham Bell, 3225 Bettembourg, Luxembourg, with registered number B159.818 - the "data controller") and its group companies (collectively, "OnLive" or "we" or "us") respect your concerns about privacy. This policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to the personal information we collect on the following, which we will refer to as the "OnLive Services" or the "Services": * onlive.com and any other OnLive-owned websites that link to this Privacy Policy (the "OnLive Websites" or "Websites") * OnLive Game Service; * Other OnLive-owned apps and software that link to this Privacy Policy; and * OnLive Customer Service ("OnLive CS"). Our Services offer connectivity with a growing number of services provided by third parties, such as social networks, content providers, platforms, communications tools, plugins and widgets of many varieties (collectively, "Third Party Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services. Third Party Services’ privacy practices are subject to their own policies. This Privacy Policy describes our collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information. 1\. Information We Obtain Information You Submit You may choose to provide us with information through the Services, such as: * Contact information, such as your name, email address, telephone number and mailing address. * Date of birth. * Information obtained from the Facebook account you associate with the Services and all information available to us through the Facebook Application Programming Interface. * Login credentials for Third Party Services that you would like to use through the Services. * Payment card information and related billing details. * Communications within our Services (such as email, instant messaging sessions, video, text chats, voice communications, friend requests, and online group activity) and related information. We may monitor all communications taking place through our Services. For example, if a user of the OnLive Game Service uses voice chat to talk to another user, their conversation may be recorded as part of a Brag Clip® video. * Other content you submit or create on the Services. * Information relevant to candidacy for employment with us, such as your resume, if you apply for a job with us. Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software In general, when you use the apps and other software that are part of the OnLive Service, we may collect the following information by automated means: * Information about your computer or other device and related hardware, including identification details (e.g., MAC address). * Information about your operating system, platform and other software you use in connection with the Services. * IP address of your device. * Information about your network connection and your ISP. * The times of your connection to our Services. * Information about your use of the software. Please see the following sections for more details regarding automated collection by the OnLive Game Service. OnLive Game Service In addition to the information discussed in the introduction to the "Information We Collect by Automated Means With Apps and Other Software" section, the OnLive Game Service also uses automated means to collect and create information such as the following: * All of your gameplay, including everything you hear, see, say or do while playing or otherwise interacting with a game or its settings. This includes, for example, all voice chat, notifications, friend requests and responses, and all other communications with the Services and with other people that take place within the game, as well as your Player Tag or Screen Name. * Player Profiles, which are a combination of information you submit and information we collect by automated means. These personal summaries may include the user’s Player Tag, presence on the Services, last log-on, use of content, gameplay statistics, and stated city, region or country location that can be seen on the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service. * All other aspects of your interaction with the OnLive Game Service, such as your interaction with its main settings. * Your interactions with certain Third Party Services or about your use of certain Third Party Services in connection with the OnLive Game Service, (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). Information We Collect by Automated Means On Our Websites * When you use our Websites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, Clear GIFs, and website and service logs, (whether or not your Web browser issues "Do Not Track" signals). * Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information that are stored by your browser on the hard drive or memory of your computer or other Internet access device. Cookies may enable us to personalize your experience on the Websites, maintain a persistent session, passively collect demographic information about your computer and monitor advertisements and other activities. For example, cookies can advise us whether you have visited one of the OnLive Websites previously, and/or may contain other information that will facilitate your next visit to one of the OnLive Websites. We do not intentionally collect any personal information through our use of cookies, although they may identify your computer. Our Websites may use HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html] and Global Storage Settings Panel [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager03.html]. The decision to disable cookies, however, may prevent you from being able to use certain portions of the OnLive Websites. * Clear GIFs: Clear GIFs are small graphic images (in GIF or other image format) placed on a web page, web-based document, or in an e-mail message. Clear GIFs are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (e.g., only 1-by-1 pixel) and either transparent or the same color as the background of the web page, document or e-mail message. We do not use clear GIFs to collect personal information about you. We may, however, use clear GIFs on our Websites to capture statistical usage information for our web pages, features or other elements on a web page. We may correlate this information to a user to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on our web pages. We do not use clear GIFs in the OnLive Game Service. * Website & Service Logs: OnLive may collect information in the form of website and/or service logs (collectively "Logs"). These Logs are files that record activity on the Websites and related Services and gather statistics about users' activities, such as how many users have visited the Websites, how often, how many "hits" a particular webpage has received, sign-in and sign-off times for the Services, type and quality of the user’s Internet connection to the Services, identification of the user’s hardware and software running the Services, which features on the Services you used, and the frequency of use. The entries comprising the Logs may contain IP addresses, user IDs, email addresses, and identification of the Internet service provider that provides your connection to the Internet. Generally, we may use the Logs to (i) operate and improve the Websites and Services; (ii) identify the popularity of certain features; (iii) assist with marketing and demographic studies; (iv) enable us to assess overall efficiency and activity on the Websites and Services; and (v) assess users' web-browsing, usage, preferences, and habits on the Websites and in the OnLive Game Service. We also use the Logs to monitor traffic on the Websites and Services, to troubleshoot technical problems, to support OnLive CS operations, for security reasons, and to foster the safety of the Websites and Services. Please note that Third Party Services may collect personally identifiable information about an individual’s online activities over time and across different websites when the individual uses our Website and other Services. This may include the use of cookies which collect information from you across a number of websites including the OnLive Websites. You can choose not to accept these cookies via your browser settings. The Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information online from or market to children under the age of 13. If OnLive becomes aware that any person submitting personal information to the Websites or the Services is under the age of 13, we will promptly take steps to close the account and delete any personal information pursuant to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect In General We may use the information we collect through the Services to provide the Services and fulfill the immediate purpose for which it was requested, as well as for other purposes. Uses may include: * Providing, administering and communicating with you about products, services, events and promotions for us and our business partners (including by contacting you with newsletters and other marketing communications). * Processing, evaluating and responding to your requests, inquiries and applications. * Managing our customer information databases. * Administering contests, sweepstakes and surveys and other communications. * Customizing your experience with our Services. * Evaluating your application for employment with us. * Creating marketing content. * Operating, evaluating and improving our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research, data analytics and data appends; determining and managing the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing; analyzing our products and services; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities). * Protecting against and preventing fraud, unauthorized transactions, security issues, claims and other liabilities, and managing risk exposure and quality for our Services and Third Party Services. * Complying with and enforcing applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies and terms, such as our Terms of Service for our Services and terms imposed by Third Party Services. Analytics We may use third-party Web analytics services on our Websites, such as those of Google Analytics. These service providers use the sort of technology described in the Information We Collect By Automated Means on Our Websites section to help us analyze how users use the Websites, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive. The information collected by the technology (including your IP address) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Websites. We may also use data from Google’s interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as interests) with Google Analytics to understand our audiences. To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please click here [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout]. 3\. Sharing of Information We may share your information in a variety of ways as we provide the Services and our business evolves. * When someone becomes your friend, that person will have access to information about what games you are playing and have played as well as your communications within the Services, a list of your friends, your Player Profile, your Brag Clip™ videos, your last visit to the OnLive Game Service, date joined, total play time, play style, and motto. It is important to note that friends of your friends, and friends of these friends (up to 3 generations of friends in total), will have access to such information as well. Please consider this carefully when making or accepting a friend request. You may stop sharing information with a specific friend (and therefore, their friends) at any time by removing that friend. * By default, the Spectating feature on the OnLive Game Service makes available to all users of the OnLive Game Service continuous live viewing of your gameplay. The Brag Clip™ videos feature allows you to record short clips of your gameplay that may be viewed by others. Because live gameplay or other activity in the OnLive Game Service may be widely viewed through the Spectating feature, OnLive cautions users to avoid revealing personally identifiable information during gameplay or other activity on the Services such as when using voice chat or text. If at any time a user does not limit the viewing of Brag Clip™ videos, OnLive may from that point forward use such videos both on the Services and externally for other purposes, including demonstrations, tournaments, marketing, promotional efforts, game refinement, engineering analysis or any other purpose. * We may share information with the Third Party Services with which you choose to interact, such as by posting to your social media account. For further detail about Facebook-related sharing, visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22280346-facebook-sharing]. * We may share your information among our affiliates and joint marketing partners. * We may provide a report to our business partners that tells them who responded to a particular offer or to facilitate the fulfillment of an order that you have made with a business partner. * To help your friends find you, OnLive may allow registered users who enter your email address to find you and send you friend requests through the OnLive Game Service. For more information and instructions on how to opt out of others finding you via your email address please visit here [https://support.onlive.com/entries/22278213-Privacy-Settings]. Other Sharing * We share your information to facilitate your requests or in connection with such requests, such as when you use features specifically designed for sharing. For example, if you provide us with login credentials for a Third Party Service so that we may log you into that service, we will provide the Third Party Service with those credentials to carry out your request. * We may share information we collect on the Services with certain service providers that support our Services or perform work on our behalf. * We may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury or loss; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. * We reserve the right to transfer information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation). * We also may disclose aggregated information to third parties in a manner that does not identify particular users. Please note: * We do not consider Player Tags, Screen Names or Player Profiles to be personal information. We may use and disclose them without restriction. For example, Player Tags and Player Profiles from the OnLive Websites and OnLive Game Service (as well as the username for the Third Party Service that you use in connection with the Service) may be made public for the purposes of leaderboards, enhancing multiplayer gameplay, tournaments, marketing and promotion efforts and other business activities. The same is true of demographic information we collect through surveys (such as personal tastes and purchasing habits), unless we indicate otherwise in connection with a particular survey. * The sharing preferences within our Services generally do not affect the sharing of any information by or within Third Party Services. For more information, please see the "Your Rights and Choices" section below. 4\. Data Transfers and Safe Harbor You agree that we may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected and in particular that we may transfer it outside of the European Economic Area. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with applicable law. As described in our Safe Harbor certification [http://safeharbor.export.gov/companyinfo.aspx?id=19081], we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information received in the U.S. from European Union member countries and Switzerland. OL2, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view OL2, Inc.’s certification, please visit the Safe Harbor website [http://export.gov/safeharbor/]. If you have any questions or complaints about our handling of your personal information that we receive in connection with Safe Harbor, please contact us as described in the "How to Contact Us" section below. If we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may contact the ESRB, and we agree to resolve the matter through their processes. 5\. Your Rights and Choices Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. Where applicable, you may amend your preferences regarding how we communicate with you and make certain other privacy-related choices by updating your profile, account and settings in your OnLive authenticated account or by contacting us as described in the How to Contact Us section below. You may unsubscribe from OnLive marketing-oriented emails by following the instructions in those emails. As this Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services, and because we do not control Third Party Services, exercising your rights and choices under this section of the Privacy Policy will not affect the Third Party Services’ handling of your information. For example, the Privacy preferences screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service allows you to limit how the extent to which the OnLive Game Service itself shares your Brag Clip® videos within the OnLive Game Service. That setting applies only within the OnLive Game Service. If you access games through a Third Party Service, the Third Party Service's sharing settings — and not the sharing settings of the OnLive Game Service itself — will apply to how the Third Party Service shares information. Be sure to familiarize yourself with the privacy settings — and their defaults — of each Third Party Service with which you interact, as they generally operate independently from those of the OnLive Services. In some cases, we may build features into our Services that are specially designed to allow you to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. These features will be clearly labeled to highlight this functionality. For example, you can use the Facebook Sharing screen in the Settings menu of the OnLive Game Service to make certain adjustments to what the OnLive Game Service will ask Facebook to post to your wall. In some cases, settings within the Third Party Services may be used to adjust how our OnLive Services interact with Third Party Services. For example, a Third Party Service may allow you to enter an authentication key or other credential through our OnLive Game Service that may allow you to remain logged in to the Third Party Service through our OnLive Game Service, even when you are not using the OnLive Game Service; you may be able to contact the Third Party Service to revoke that credential or adjust how it works. 6\. Security We take reasonable technical and organizational safety measures that we believe may help protect against unauthorized access to our Services, however we note that no security is perfect. 7\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our practice. When such updates occur we will revise the date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you. 8\. ESRB Certification This Privacy Policy and the certification seal confirm that OnLive is a valid licensee and participating member in the Entertainment Software Rating Board ("ESRB") Privacy Certified Program. To protect your privacy, we have voluntarily undertaken this privacy initiative. The ESRB has reviewed and certified that the OnLive Services meet established online information collection and use practices. As part of the ESRB certification program, we are subject to frequent audits of our Websites and other enforcement and accountability mechanisms administered independently by the ESRB. 9\. How to Contact Us If you have any comments, questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy or our information collection practices, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please send us a detailed message via email at privacy@onlive.com or via regular mail to OnLive EMEA S.à r.l (4, Rue Graham Bell, 3225 Bettembourg, Luxembourg) , Attn: Privacy Policy Administrator and Legal Department. Thank you.
